ezlocal.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | EZlocal

## EZlocal Privacy Policy

**

Updated 6/24/09

**

EZlocal is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors of our website. This privacy statement describes what we do with the information that we receive about you when you visit our website. The information that we receive about you depends on what you do when you visit our website. This information may be expanded or updated as we change or develop our site. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time-to-time to see if anything has changed. Your continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of our Privacy Policy.

### What is our Commitment to You? 

EZlocal wants your experiences at our website (our "Site") to be fun and exciting. We know how important your privacy is and we have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to preserving your privacy. When you use the Site, you will sometimes be asked to give us personal information. We are sensitive to your privacy concerns, and are committed to letting you know what information is being collected on the Site, how the information is being used and what choices you have regarding the collection and use of the information. Please take a moment to review this privacy policy and feel free to contact us with any questions at privacy@ezlocal.com. 

### What Types of Information do we Collect About You and What do we do with the Information? 

If you want to participate in any of our contests or sweepstakes, you may be asked to provide some personal information. When we do this we are collecting what we refer to as "Personally Identifiable Information." Personally Identifiable Information may include your name, email address, street address, zip or postal code, country of residence, and telephone number. These questions need to be answered for you to participate in our contest and sweepstakes. We use this Personally Identifiable Information to contact you about your entry and send you your prize if you are a winner. 

Whenever you send us personal correspondence, such as email and letters, or when other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect and store such information. 

We may use your contact information to send you information about exciting products and services, important events, announcements and changes to our Site or to our policies. You may elect not to receive, or opt-out of, receiving certain information from us, but may not unsubscribe from announcements relating to our policies and the Site, unless you choose to have us delete your Personally Identifiable Information. If we delete your Personally Identifiable Information, we will not be able to maintain your entry information for any contests or sweepstakes that you have entered. 

Demographic and profile data are also collected at the Site. We use this information in order to customize our Site to analyze and enhance our Site and to distribute statistics and marketplace information about the Site. Such information will always be in the aggregate and not about individual users. 

### Do we Share Information with Third Parties? 

We do not share information with any non-affiliated third party except as permitted or required by law, such as inquires by law enforcement or to comply with Federal laws such as the Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM Act of 2003) or the Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act (FACTA). 

### Information Corrections or Changes

You have the ability to correct or change certain information in our records, such as your address and contact information. The process for changing the information occurs when you login. You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information, you can contact us via email at service@ezlocal.com. 

### Can you Opt-Out of Emails, Phone Calls or Mail at Anytime? 

Our Site provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving information from us. You may opt-out of receiving information from us by sending us an email at privacy@ezlocal.com. 

### What is our Linking Policy?

Our Site may contain links to other websites, offers and services. We urge you to review the privacy policies governing such other websites, offers, and services. We cannot, however, be responsible for the privacy practices for such websites, offers, and services. We encourage everyone to be aware when they leave this Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects Personally Identifiable Information. This privacy policy applies solely to Personally Identifiable Information collected by this Site. 

### How do we use Cookies? 

EZlocal may set and access cookies on your computer to provide you with customized content. Most cookies are “session cookies,” which automatically delete themselves from your hard drive after each session. You are always free to decline these cookies if your browser permits, however, you may not be able to use certain features. 

Like many Internet companies, EZlocal may automatically track information based upon your behavior on our Site. We use this information for research purposes to better understand, protect and service our customers. The information we track may include such information as browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, IP address and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Sites, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. EZlocal respects your privacy and this information is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as may be needed to prevent fraud or abuse of the Site. EZlocal works with third parties to serve ads on our Sites. These ads may contain cookies and/or action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness and gather completely anonymous information. We have no access to or control over these cookies or action tags. 

### How do we Protect Your Information? 

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those of our employees who need to know that information in order serve you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect your nonpublic personal information. 

### Will this Privacy Policy Change? 

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. You agree to obtain notices of, and changes to, this privacy policy electronically by visiting this Site. Therefore, we encourage you to review this Site from time to time to review changes to our privacy policy. By using our Site and its services, you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this privacy policy, you must discontinue use of our Site. 

### Do you have a Privacy Complaint? 

EZlocal takes our users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that EZlocal has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write to EZlocal at the following address or by sending and email to privacy@ezlocal.com. 

EZlocal  
377 E Butterfield Rd  
Suite 300  
Lombard, IL 60148 

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. 

Please note that EZlocal is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-EZlocal websites to which this Site or any other EZlocal website may link. Also, EZlocal is not responsible for the privacy practices of its Members, Partners or users of its Members websites. You should review the additional privacy policy of the Member or Partner site before using the site and contact the organization should you have questions regarding their policies. 

### Have more Questions Regarding our Privacy Policy?

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please e-mail us at: privacy@ezlocal.com

05645645\V-1
